RG 015, Office of Policy and Management
Connecticut State Library
Office of Policy & Management records
1907-2004
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. Office of Policy & Management
252.25 cubic feet
The Office of Policy and Management is the Connecticut governor's staff agency. It provides information and analysis that the Governor uses to formulate public policy goals for the State and assist State agencies and municipalities in implementing policy decisions on behalf of the people of Connecticut.
RG015
Multiple
Historical Note
In 1897, The General Assembly created a Board of Control to approve increases in appropriation made by the legislature (Chapter 168, P.A. of 1897). The Board consisted of the Governor, Treasurer and Comptroller. In 1915, The Assembly established a Board of Finance to meet with the Legislative Joint Standing Committee on Appropriations to organize and approve bills and resolutions on state appropriations (Chapter 302, P.A. of 1915). The Board of Finance included the Comptroller, Treasurer, Tax Commissioner, and three electors appointed by the Governor. In 1927, legislative action abolished the two boards and transferred their functions to a Board of Finance and Control. This new board consisted of the Governor as ex officio chairman, the Secretary of the State, Treasurer, Comptroller, Attorney General, Tax Commissioner, three electors appointed by the Governor. The Commissioner of Finance and Control sat as an ex officio member and administrative secretary (Chapter 297, P.A. of 1927).
In 1937, Governor Wilbur Cross' Commission on the Reorganization of State Government recommended that the legislature elevate the Office of the Commissioner of Finance and Control to the Department of Finance and Control. It did so (Chapter 380, P.A. of 1937). The Assembly transferred the old Board of Finance and Control's function to a Finance Advisory Committee in 1943. The Governor, Lt. Governor, Comptroller, Treasurer, five members of the legislative committees on appropriations made up the membership. The Commissioner of Finance and Control served as secretary (Chapter 1, P.A. 1943).
In 1977, the Assembly created the Office of Policy and Management (OPM) to replace the Department of Finance and Control (Public Act 77-614). In addition to creating a Department of Administrative Services, OPM was the first phase of an executive branch reorganization in 1979. OPM aids the Governor in "policy formation, program development and executive." OPM also develops a "continuing integrated process of program design, resource allocation, and performance evaluation."
Since its inception, the agency has gone through a number of internal reorganizations. It originally consisted of seven divisions: Energy; Budget and Financial Management; Comprehensive Planning; Intergovernmental Relations; Management and Evaluation; Employment and Training; and Criminal Justice. As of 2007 there are eight divisions: Budget and Financial Management Division; Criminal Justice Policy and Planning Division; Office of Finance; Intergovernmental Policy Division; Office of Labor Relations; Policy Development and Planning Division; Office of Transportation Policy; Division of Administration.
See also the.
Scope and Content
In addition to the records of OPM and its predecessors, included here are records from various commissions and offices that are or have been under OPM for administrative purposes. These include: Governor's Council on Voluntary Action (eliminated in 1991); Blue Ribbon Commission on Housing; Energy Advisory Board; and Office of Family Support.
Arrangement
Series 1a. Board of Control, 1907-1926, Accession: 1983-003, 1.5 cubic feet
Includes minutes arranged chronologically.
Series 1b. Board of Finance and Control, 1927-1962, 7.25 cubic feet
Accession: 1983-003, Minutes, 1927-1937, 3.5 cubic feet
Accession: 1986-004, Budget expenditure authorizations, 1937-1962, 3.75 cubic feet
Series 2. State Boards and Commissions, 1963-1965, Accession: 1983-003, 1 cubic foot
Minutes arranged alphabetically by board.
Series 3. Office of State Planning, 1960-1973, 14 cubic feet
Accession: 1983-003, Land use studies and reports, 1963-1973, 2 cubic feet
Accession: T000711, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program drawings, 1960-1972, 12 cubic feet (15 bundles)
Series 4. Budget Division, 1955-1961, Accession: 1983-003, 1 cubic foot
County records.
Series 5. Finance Advisory Committee, 1943-1981, Accession: 1983-003, 50.5 cubic feet
Minutes, 1948-1969; Budget allotment or adjustment requests, 1943-1981.
Series 6. Special Bond Commission, 1941-1967, Accession: 1983-003, 1 cubic foot
Minutes.
Series 7. State Bond Commission, 1953-1988, 9 cubic feet
Accession: 1983-003, Minutes, 1953-1977, 5 cubic feet.
Accession: 1995-013, Hearing Files, 1987-1988, 4 cubic feet
Series 8. Board of Equalization, 1925-1927, Accession: 1999-099, 1 cubic foot
Minutes, 1925-1927, 1 volume
Series 9. Public Works funds allotments, 1938-1940, Accession: 1983-003, 1 volume
Series 10. Scrapbooks, 1927-1939, Accession: T003187, 6 cubic feet.
Series 11. Commission on State Institutions, 1919-1948, Accession: T000685, 1 cubic foot
Collections ledger, 1919-1948, 1 volume
Series 12. Planning and Budgeting, circa 1971-1972, Accession: 2004-026, 22 cubic feet
Millstone Nuclear Power Station, circa 1971-1972
Series 13. Comprehensive Planning Division, 1957-1991, 28 cubic feet
Accession: 1985-026B, Community Development Block Grants, 1970-1977, 4.5 cubic feet Accession: 1986-010C, Community Development Block Grants, 1976-1977, 3.5 cubic feet Accession: 1991-028, General Files, 1976-1979, 12 cubic feet Accession: 1996-030, Administrative Records, 1957-1991, 8 cubic feet
Series 14. Management and Justice Planning Division, 1979-1987, Accession: 1989-069, 16 cubic feet
Subject Files
Series 15. Energy Division, 1960-1990, 31.25 cubic feet
Accession: 1990-007, Coastal Energy Impact Program, 1977-1986, 5 cubic feet.
Accession: 1992-014, Atomic Energy Coordinator, 1966-1969, 1979-1983, .25 cubic feet.
Accession: 2002-068, Atomic Energy Coordinator, 1960-1977, 2 cubic feet.
Accession: 1996-012, Files, 1972-1990, 24 cubic feet.
Series 16. Secretary, 1980-1998, 31 cubic feet
Accession: 1980-1990, Anthony V. Milano, 1980-1990, 27 cubic feet
Accession: 2003-009, William Cibes, Reginald Jones, Michael Koslowski, Lori Aronson (Deputy), Donald Downs (Deputy), 1991-1998, 4 cubic feet.
Series 17. Governor's Council on Voluntary Action, 1979-1991, Accession: 1992-035, 11 cubic feet
Administrative files and annual conference materials.
Series 18. Department of Planning and Engery Policy, 1977, Accession: 1999-036, 0.25 cubic feet
Energy conservation plan report
Series 29. Office of Labor Relations, 1994-1995, Accession: 1999-076
Series 20. Specialized State-Operated Services Committee of the Juvenile Justice Reorganization Plan, 1994-1995, Accession: 2001-070, 0.50 cubic feet
Series 21. Blue Ribbon Commission on Housing, 1987-1988, Accession: 2001-074, 0.25 cubic feet
Joan Maloney files.
Series 22. Connecticut Census Data Center, 1985,1988, 3 cubic feet
Accession: 2004-029, Social Indicators for Planning and Evaluation, 1985, 2 cubic feet
Accession: 2004-030, Job Training Partnership Act Eligibility Report, 1988, 1 cubic foot
Series 23. Energy Advisory Board, 1974-2003, Accession: 2006-003, 2 cubic feet
Minutes.
Series 24. Office of Family Support, 2001-2004, Accession: 2007-037, 3.75 cubic feet
Related Material
RG 061 County Government
RG 071 Department of Housing contains more records on community planning.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. Blue Ribbon Commission on Housing; Connecticut. Board of Control; Connecticut. Dept. of Finance and Control; Connecticut Energy Advisory Board; Connecticut. Governor's Council on Voluntary Action; Connecticut. Office of Family Support; Connecticut. Office of Policy & Management; Connecticut. State Board of Finance
Persons:
Aronson, Lorraine M; Cibes, William Joseph, 1943-; Downs, Donald; Jones, Reginald L., Jr; Koslowski, Michael; Maloney, Joan; Milano, Anthony V
Subjects:
Connecticut. Board of Control -- Records and correspondence; Connecticut. Dept. of Finance and Control -- Records and correspondence; Connecticut. Office of Policy & Management -- Records and correspondence; Connecticut. State Board of Finance -- Records and correspondence; County government -- Connecticut; Finance, Public -- Connecticut; Political planning -- Connecticut
Document Types:
Agendas (administrative records); Correspondence; Minutes; News clippings; Registers (lists); Reports
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Series 1a. Board of Control, 1907-1926; 1983-003; 1.5 cubic feet
  - Minutes, 1907-1926
    The volumes not stored in boxes are not numbered in chronological order.
    - 1907-1913, 1 volume (Box Box 1)
    - 1914-1918, 1 volume (Box Box 1)
    - 1919-1920, 1 volume (Box Box 1)
    - 1921 January 11 - 1924 March 13, 1 volume (Box Volume 4)
    - 1924 March 20 - 1926 December 31, 1 volume (Box Volume 7)
- Series 1b. Board of Finance and Control, 1927-1962; 7.25 cubic feet
  - 1983-003, 3.5 cubic feet
    - Minutes, 1927-1937; 19 volumes
      - 1927 January 6 - 1929 August 1, 1 volume (Box Volume 1)
      - 1929 August 8 - 1931 August 6, 1 volume (Box Volume 2)
      - 1931 August 13 - 1934 January 11, 1 volume (Box Volume 5)
      - 1934 January 18 - 1935 June 27, 1 volume (Box Volume 3)
      - 1935 July 11 - 1936 June 18, 1 volume (Box Volume 6)
      - 1935 July 11 - 1936 June 18, 1 volume (Box Box 3)
        This is a second copy of these meeting dates.
      - 1936 July 2 - 1937 May 20, 2 volumes (2 copies) (Box Box 3)
      - 1937 January 7 - 1937 May 20, 1 volume (Box Box 3)
      - Indexes, 2 volumes (Box Box 3)
  - 1986-004, 3.75 cubic feet
    - Budget expenditure authorizations, 1937-1962
      - 1937 May 25-1938 March 16 (Volume Volume 1)
      - 1938 March 16-July 1 (Volume Volume 2)
      - 1938 July 7-November 16 (Volume Volume 3)
      - 1938 November 1-1939 February 7 (Volume Volume 4)
      - 1939 February 7-May 27 (Volume Volume 5)
      - 1939 May 27-September 14 (Volume Volume 6)
      - 1939 September 15-1940 January 9 (Volume Volume 7)
      - 1939 December 22-1940 April 10 (Volume Volume 8)
      - 1940 April 22-June 21 (Volume Volume 9)
      - 1940 June 21-September 26 (Volume Volume 10)
      - 1940 September 26-December 14 (Volume Volume 11)
      - 1938 December 18-1941 March 14 (Volume Volume 12)
      - 1941 March 12-December 31 (Volume Volume 13)
      - 1941 June 17-August 21 (Volume Volume 14)
      - 1941 August 19-October 30 (Volume Volume 15)
      - 1941 October 30-December 15 (Volume Volume 16)
      - 1948 December 17-1956 February 14 (Volume Volume 17)
      - 1956 February 14-1959 May 21 (Volume Volume 18)
      - 1959 May 20-1962 January 31 (Volume Volume 19)
- Series 2. State Boards and Commissions, 1963-1965; 1983-003; 1 cubic foot
  - Minutes, 1963-1965 (Box 4)
    - Accountancy, Board of (Box 4)
    - Agricultural experiment Station, Board of Control (Box 4)
    - Agriculture and Natural Resources, Council on (Box 4)
    - Alcoholism Division (Box 4)
    - Boating Safety, Commission on (Box 4)
    - Civil Rights Commission (Box 4)
    - Civil Service Commission (Box 4)
    - Dental Commission (Box 4)
    - Development Commission (Box 4)
    - Embalmers and Funeral Directors, Board of Examiners of (Box 4)
    - Farmington River Valley Flood Control Commission (Box 4)
    - Greater Hartford Flood Commission (Box 4)
    - Harbor Commissioners, Board of (Box 4)
    - Healing Arts, Board of (Box 4)
    - Hypertrichologists, Board of Examiners of (Box 4)
    - Industrial Building Commission (Box 4)
    - Medical Examining Board (Box 4)
    - Mental Health Planning Project Advisory Council (Box 4)
    - Natureopathic Examiners, Board of (Box 4)
    - Nursing, Board of Examiners for (Box 4)
    - Opticians, Commission of (Box 4)
    - Optometry, Board of Examiners in (Box 4)
    - Osteopathic Examining Board (Box 4)
    - Penal institutions (Box 4)
    - Physical Therapists, Board of Examiners for (Box 4)
    - Podiatry, Board of Examiners in (Box 4)
    - Psychologists, Board of Examiners of (Box 4)
    - Retirement Commission (Box 4)
    - Safety Commission (Box 4)
    - State hospitals and institutions (Box 4)
    - Steamship Terminals, Commissioners of (Box 4)
    - Temporary commissions (Box 4)
    - Traffic Commission (Box 4)
    - Tree Protection Examining Board (Box 4)
    - Veterinary Registration and Examination, Board of (Box 4)
- Series 3. Office of State Planning, 1960-1973; 14 cubic feet
  For records after 1973, see Comprehensive Planning Division.
  - 1983-003, 2 cubic feet
    - Land use studies and reports, 1963-1973
      - Proposed A Plan of Conservation and Development for Connecticut, Office of State Planning, 1973 January (Box 5)
      - Resource Industries, Technical Report 141, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1963 June (Box 5)
      - Planning Connecticut's Regional Communities, Connecticut Development Commission, 1966 (Box 5)
      - A Comprehensive State-wide Land Use, Resources and Transportation Planning Effort, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, undated (Box 5)
      - STEPS to the Establishment of Regional Planning Agencies in Connecticut, Revised, 1970 (Box 5)
      - Inventory of Published Data, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1968 (Box 5)
      - Status of Connecticut Planning Regions, Office of State Planning, 1971 (Box 5)
      - Connecticut's Readiness to Meet the Impact of Reduction of Defense Expenditure, State Planning Council, 1969 November (Box 5)
      - Airport Facilities Plan for the State of Connecticut, Appendix, Frederic R. Harris Associates, Consulting Engineers, 1968 October (Box 5)
      - A Model Framework for Recreation Planning in Connecticut, Summary Report, Alan M. Voorhees & Associates, Inc., 1966 October (Box 5)
      - A Model Framework for Recreation Planning in Connecticut, Alan M. Voorhees & Associates, Inc., 1966 June (Box 5)
      - Status in "67" A Report on Regional Planning in Connecticut, CDC, 1967 April (Box 5)
      - Connecticut Local Government Expenditures-Revenues, 1940-1980, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1969 June (Box 5)
      - Airport Facilities Plan for the State of Connecticut, Final Report, Frederic R. Harris Associates, 1969 April (Box 5)
      - Index of Open Space Studies, Technical Report 341, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1967 (Box 5)
      - Connecticut: Choices For Action-Urban Development, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1966 (Box 5)
      - Connecticut: Choices for Action-The Economy, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1966 (Box 5)
      - Connecticut: Choices for Action-The Green Land, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1966 (Box 5)
      - Connecticut: Choices for Action-Choices for Action-Highlights, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1967 (Box 5)
      - Connecticut: Choices for Action-Transportation, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1966 (Box 5)
      - Connecticut: Choices for Action-Goals for Connecticut, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1966 (Box 5)
      - Manufacturing Industries, Technical Report 143, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1963 November (Box 5)
      - Community Services, Technical Report 150, Part 2, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1963 October (Box 5)
      - Government Organization, Technical Report 156, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1964 August (Box 5)
      - Connecticut Takes Stock for Action, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1964 June (Box 5)
      - Regional Planning Publications in Connecticut, Bibliography, Office of State Planning, Revised 1970 (Box 5)
      - P-42 Staff Paper #261, Financial Assistance Programs of the Federal Government, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, undated (Box 5)
      - A Guide to Determining Costs of a Child Day Care Center, State Planning Council, Child Day Care Task Force, 1970 December (Box 5)
      - Connecticut State Agency Responsibilities in Housing, Office of State Planning, 1970 November (Box 5)
      - Bibliography, Selected Regional, State and Other Governmental Agency Water Resources Planning Documents, Office of State Planning, 1970 April (Box 5)
      - Statewide Long-Range Plan for the Management of The Water Resources of Connecticut Phase I Report, Office of State Planning, 1971 (Box 5)
      - Connecticut State Agencies Planning or Administrative Districts, State Planning Council, 1969 May (Box 5)
      - The Appearance of Connecticut, Technical Report 122, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1963 February (Box 5)
      - Public Finance, Technical Report 157, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1963 November (Box 5)
      - Population Density of Connecticut Planning Regions, Appendix Table 16, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, undated (Box 5)
      - Physical Geography, Technical Report 111, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1963 September (Box 6)
      - Water, Technical Report 124, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1963 May (Box 6)
      - Population, Technical Report 131, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1962 November (Box 6)
      - Labor Force, Technical Report 132, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1963 September (Box 6)
      - Service Industries, Technical Report 144, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1963 September (Box 6)
      - Transportation, Technical Report 153, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1964 April (Box 6)
      - Attitudes of Connecticut People, Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1966 (Box 6)
      - Economic Assets and Liabilities-Services to Industry, P-42 Staff Paper #221A, undated (Box 6)
      - Economic Assets and Liabilities-Capital, P-42 Staff Paper #221B, undated (Box 6)
      - Economic Assets and Liabilities-Fuel, Power and Water, P-42 Staff Paper #221C, undated (Box 6)
      - Economic Assets and Liabilities-The Work Force, P-42 Staff Paper #221D, undated (Box 6)
      - Economic Assets and Liabilities-Amenities, P-42 Staff Paper #221E, undated (Box 6)
      - Economic Assets and Liabilities-Management, P-42 Staff Paper #221F, undated (Box 6)
      - Economic Assets and Liabilities-Access to Materials & Markets, P-42 Staff Paper #221G, undated (Box 6)
      - Economic Assets and Liabilities-Major Industries of Connecticut, P-42 Staff Paper #223A, undated (Box 6)
      - Defense Employment, P-42 Staff Paper #223B, undated (Box 6)
      - Vacant Land Characteristics, P-42 Staff Paper #231, undated (Box 6)
      - Open Space-Recreation - Shellfish Resources, P-42 Staff Paper #241C, undated (Box 6)
      - Open Space-Recreation - Recreation Demand, P-42 Staff Paper #242B, undated (Box 6)
      - Non-Highway Transportation - General Aviation, P-42 Staff Paper #251A, undated (Box 6)
      - Non-Highway Transportation - Water Transportation, P-42 Staff Paper #251B, undated (Box 6)
      - New Modes of Transportation, P-42 Staff Paper #251C, undated (Box 6)
      - Non-Highway Transportation - Railroad Passenger Service, P-42 Staff Paper #251D, undated (Box 6)
      - Transportation Impedance Study, P-42 Staff Paper #511, undated (Box 6)
      - Transportation Network Selection & Classification, P-42 Staff Paper #512, undated (Box 6)
      - Transportation - Traffic Counting Program, P-42 Staff Paper #527, undated (Box 6)
      - Transportation - Goods Movement Projection and Distribution Model, P-42 Staff Paper #532, undated (Box 6)
      - Transportation - Census Data, P-42 Staff Paper #551, undated (Box 6)
      - Analysis of Land Abutting Navigable Waterway to Define Potential Industrial Areas, P-42 Staff Paper relating to 231F & 251B, undated (Box 6)
      - Employment in Connecticut, 1970 - 2000, P-67 Staff Paper #323, 1967 October (Box 6)
      - Construction Employment in Connecticut 1960 - 2000, P-67 Staff Paper #325, 1967 November (Box 6)
      - Transit, P-67 Staff Paper #536, undated (Box 6)
      - Planning for the Future, Connecticut's Major Corridor Needs Present to Year 2000 Connecticut Highway Dept., Bureau of Planning & Design, 1968 September (Box 6)
  - T000711, 12 cubic feet
    - Connecticut Interregional Planning Program drawings, 1960-1972; 15 bundles
- Series 4. Budget Division, 1955-1961; 1983-003; 1 cubic foot
  - County records, 1955-1961 (Box 7)
    Working papers and correspondence regarding account closures, property transfers, etc. after the abolishment of county governments effective October 1, 1960. The records include personnel, property, real estate lists, county commissioners' reports, and the Auditors of Public Accounts' finance report.
- Series 5. Finance Advisory Committee, 1943-1981; 1983-003; 50.5 cubic feet
  - Minutes, 1958-1969; 1 volume (Box 8)
  - Budget allotment or adjustment requests, 1943-1981
    - Transactions
      - 1943 June 2-1955 November 7, 1 volume (Box 9)
      - 1945 November-1947 June 24, 1 volume (Box 9)
      - 1947 June 24-1949 June 2, 1 volume (Box 9)
      - 1949 June 2-1951 July 11, 1 volume (Box 9)
      - 1951 July 11-1954 April 7, 1 volume (Box 10)
      - 1954 April 7-1956 March 7, 1 volume (Box 10)
      - 1954 April 7-1956 March 7, 1 volume (Box 10)
      - 1956 March 7-1956 December 7, 1 volume (Box 10)
      - 1956 December 7-1958 May 3, 1 volume (Box 10)
      - 1958 May 7-1960 October 3, 1 volume (Box 10)
      - 1960 October 3-1962 August 8, 1 volume (Box 11)
      - 1962 August 8-1964 June 5, 1 volume (Box 11)
      - 1964 July 1-1965 June 30, 1 volume (Box 11)
      - 1965 July 7-1966 June 27, 1 volume (Box 11)
      - 1966 July 12-1967 June 7, 1 volume (Box 11)
      - 1967 July 5-1968 June 13, 1 volume (Box 11)
      - 1968 July 3-1969 June 4, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - Budget adjustments
      Boxes are labeled "Budget Allotments".
      - 1958 January 7-June 30, 1 volume (Box 17)
      - 1958 July 3-1959 February 27, 1 volume (Box 17)
      - 1959 March 6-July 30, 1 volume (Box 17)
      - 1959 August 4-1960 January 29, 1 volume (Box 17)
      - 1960 February 1-June 30, 1 volume (Box 18)
      - 1960 July 1-December 30, 1 volume (Box 18)
      - 1961 January 5-January 28, 1 volume (Box 18)
      - 1961 July 3-October 20, 1 volume (Box 18)
      - 1961 November 1-1962 February 21, 1 volume (Box 19)
      - 1962 March 1-May 28, 1 volume (Box 19)
      - 1962 March 1-May 28, 1 volume (Box 19)
      - 1962 September 4-November 30, 1 volume (Box 19)
      - 1962 December 4-1963 February 28, 1 volume (Box 19)
      - 1963 March 1-May 14, 1 volume (Box 20)
      - 1963 May 15-July 11, 1 volume (Box 20)
      - 1963 September 12-December 4, 1 volume (Box 20)
      - 1962 December 4-1964 February 13, 1 volume (Box 20)
      - 1963 December 4-1964 February 13, 1 volume (Box 20)
      - 1964 February 13-April 14, 1 volume (Box 20)
      - 1964 April 14-June 16, 1 volume (Box 21)
      - 1964 June 16-July 31, 1 volume (Box 21)
      - 1964 August 3-October 9, 1 volume (Box 21)
      - 1964 October 13-December 31, 1 volume (Box 21)
      - 1965 January 5-March 11, 1 volume (Box 21)
      - 1965 March 11-May 14, 1 volume (Box 21)
      - 1965 May 14-July 13, 1 volume (Box 22)
      - 1965 July 13-September 2, 1 volume (Box 22)
      - 1965 September 2-October 26, 1 volume (Box 22)
      - 1965 October 28-December 15, 1 volume (Box 22)
      - 1965 December 15-1966 February 10, 1 volume (Box 22)
      - 1966 February 10-March 31, 1 volume (Box 22)
      - 1966 April 4-May 10, 1 volume (Box 23)
      - 1966 May 11-June 23, 1 volume (Box 23)
      - 1966 June 25-August 5, 1 volume (Box 23)
      - 1966 August 5-September 15, 1 volume (Box 23)
      - 1966 September 16-October 31, 1 volume (Box 23)